<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Prude.degreeDatas.0.label>prude</Prude.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Prude.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME hates the sight of the human body. HECAP will be extremely unhappy when naked, more displeased than usual in tattered or worn-out clothing, and dislike the sight of other naked people.</Prude.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Insomniac.degreeDatas.0.label>insomniac</Insomniac.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Insomniac.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME will find it difficult to fall asleep because of HIS condition. HECAP will stay up longer and probably be tired a lot.</Insomniac.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <BleedingHeart.degreeDatas.0.label>bleeding heart</BleedingHeart.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <BleedingHeart.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME has a big heart and gets very emotional. HECAP loves helping people, and abhors violence and injustice. HE is more affected by these things than others.</BleedingHeart.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Gourmet.degreeDatas.0.label>gourmet</Gourmet.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Gourmet.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME is always a critic when it comes to food. HECAP expects to be fed well and will complain if HIS meals aren't up to par.</Gourmet.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Unstable.degreeDatas.0.label>unstable</Unstable.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Unstable.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME is more prone to random mood swings, which can be more severe than normal for others.</Unstable.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Lecher.degreeDatas.0.label>lecher</Lecher.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Lecher.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME is unabashedly lecherous and a thoughtless heartbreaker. HECAP will hit on anyone HE desires with no regard for the consequences.</Lecher.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Codependent.degreeDatas.0.label>codependent</Codependent.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Codependent.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME is romantically needy and won't be happy unless in a relationship. HECAP will be devastated by infidelity and breakups.</Codependent.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Outdoorsy.degreeDatas.0.label>outdoorsy</Outdoorsy.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Outdoorsy.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME loves to be outside. HECAP gets a mood bonus when there is no roof over HIS head.</Outdoorsy.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Pluviophile.degreeDatas.0.label>pluviophile</Pluviophile.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Pluviophile.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME likes the rain. HECAP gets a mood bonus when it's pouring outside, especially if HE gets to go out in it.</Pluviophile.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Photosensitive.degreeDatas.0.label>photosensitive</Photosensitive.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Photosensitive.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME has eyes, either through gene modding or random mutation, that are extremely light-sensitive. HECAP finds bright light extremely painful and indoor lighting bothersome, and will be happiest in the dark.</Photosensitive.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Socialite.degreeDatas.0.label>socialite</Socialite.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Socialite.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME loves to party! HISCAP mere presence inspires more parties in the colony, because everyone enjoys partying with HIM.</Socialite.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Desensitized.degreeDatas.0.label>desensitized</Desensitized.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Desensitized.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME has seen enough violence and death that it no longer shocks HIM like it used to.</Desensitized.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <HeavySleeper.degreeDatas.0.label>heavy sleeper</HeavySleeper.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <HeavySleeper.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME sleeps like a rock, never bothered by adverse sleeping conditions, but is difficult to wake up.</HeavySleeper.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <Polygamous.degreeDatas.0.label>polyamorous</Polygamous.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Polygamous.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME doesn't see any problem with having multiple partners. HECAP doesn't mind if HIS partner romances other people, but will not be happy in a monogamous relationship.</Polygamous.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <OpenMinded.degreeDatas.0.label>open-minded</OpenMinded.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <OpenMinded.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME sees people for what they are on the inside, not the outside. HECAP doesn't judge others for their appearances.</OpenMinded.degreeDatas.0.description>


</LanguageData>
